>> 扬声器 2: 它是否只包含到最接近的悬念 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Does it just bubble
up to the nearest suspense?
> > Brian Holt: Mm - hm，所以如果你有一个以上的话，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Mm-hm, so
if you had one above that,
它会击中最接近的一个
it would hit the first closest one, yeah.
> > Brian Holt: 我认为如果你没有，我就会崩溃，我不确定。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And I think it just crashes
if you don't have one, I'm not sure.
>> Brian Holt: 所以 Facebook 说他们在到处使用悬念。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So Facebook says that
they're using suspense everywhere.
嗯。
Yeah.
>演讲者 3: 与 Parcel 相比，有什么不同吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Is there anything different
about using this with Parcel versus
Webpack?
>> Brian Holt: Nope，他们的工作方式相同。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Nope,
they work the same way.
是啊他们俩都是
Yeah, so they both look for
该导入关键字， >> Brian Holt: And
this import keyword,
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
他们会在那个点上巧妙地分开他们都知道怎么做
they'll split intelligently on that
point and they both know how to do it.
也许机器的运作方式有点不同
Maybe mechanically it works
a little bit differently, but
懒惰来自 React ，懒惰知道怎么处理。
lazy comes from React and so
lazy knows how to handle it.
>> Brian Holt: 与累积情况相同。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Same with rollup as well.
这就是代码分割。
So that's code splitting.
没有比这更多的了
There's not a lot more to it than that.
这是一种相当简单的技术，尤其是懒的，懒惰的，悬念的。
It's a fairly easy technique, especially
with lazy now, lazy and suspense.
如果你看这个课程的 V1 和 V2
If you watch V1 and V2 of this course,
这就更难做了
this used to be a lot
more difficult to do.
而且它越来越容易了，这很酷。
[LAUGH] And it's just getting easier,
which is cool.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，这就是代码分割的结尾。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
that's the end of code splitting.
所以我要把雷波恢复得真快
So I'm gonna go reset
my repo really quick.
> > Brian Holt: 我在这里会这样做，相反。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I'll do that in here,
rather.
> > Brian Holt: 所以我要说 git reset HEAD --hard，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
I'm gonna say git reset HEAD --hard,
然后我就会说它是干净的
and then I'm gonna say git clean -f.
然后我会说 npm 的安装
And then I'm gonna say npm install.
再次，如果要检查该输出，那么将调用该可用分支
Again, if you want to check that out, the
branch of that that's available is called
代码分割，它在 GitHub 存储库上。
code splitting and
it is on the GitHub repo.